militaryfactory.com 2010-04-07

# The Military Factory Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**  
**Secrets, secrets are no fun; secrets, secrets hurt someone.**

_UPDATED: 12/3/2009_

Your privacy is important to us!

**Stat Tracking**

MilitaryFactory.com does not collect any personal information about you during your visit to our website. We have no interest in you as a person, only as an anonymous entity with observable behavioral patterns. As such we do collect standard traffic and user habit information that most every other website you visit collects. This information is used to gain a better understanding of user behavior and traffic patterns to which we can use to provide a better user experience on our website in the future. The statistical tracking allows up to see what technologies our users are viewing the site with and allows us to make changes to our site to accommodate this technology. 

For your information, the following is the only information we collect during a typical visit to our website:

  * Browser Type and Resolution
  * Operating System
  * IP Address
  * Entry Page, Pages Visited in Order of Visit and Exit Page
  * Inbound Links from whence you came to our website (if coming from another website's link)

So rest assured that no personal information of yours is being collected, tracked and reviewed. We collect information that is completely anonymous and is information that is tracked by most any other website you visit on any given day. 

So, in short, we don't care if you're Jim-Bob from Po-Dunk, USA - but we do care about why anonymous user "34.546.77.45" came to our site for only 5 seconds before deciding to leave. So we'd research what page(s) that anonymous user visited, how he/she came to our site and why that user might have left so quickly, addressing the issue by perhaps providing more relevant content to our website pages for any future visits to our site by that visitor. 

For a real-time example of what is tracked and what isn't, you can always visit our publicly-displayed traffic stats information [here](http://extremetracking.com/open;unique?login=m1l1fact).

**3rd Party Advertisements - Google Adsense**

You will notice that we use third party advertisements on MilitaryFactory.com to support our site.  Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and sometimes whether you have the Flash player installed or not.  This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

In the case of Google Adsense ads, this ad server uses the DoubleClick DART cookie. As per the Google website, it is explained as such:

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this website. 
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. 
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security.  However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites.  For instance, this might effect your ability to access or login to certain services or programs such as logging into forums or accounts.

**3rd Party Advertisements - BurstMedia**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

~ The MilitaryFactory.com Team
